Albert E. Waugh Papers 1988.0059
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series VI: Sundials, undated, 1929-1984
  - Sundials
    - Directions for Laying Out, undated, 1936, 1938, 1959 (Box 23, Folder 326)
    - Gnomonic Scales, undated, 1958-1959 (Box 23, Folder 327)
    - Gravestones, undated (Box 23, Folder 328)
    - Makers, undated, 1964-1981 (Box 23, Folder 329)
  - Sundials: Their Theory and Construction
    - Advertisements, undated, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 330)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 331)
    - Errata, undated, 1975, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 332)
  - T - Z, 1958-1979 (Box 24, Folder 333)
  - Unidentified, undated (Box 24, Folder 334)
  - Waugh Sundial
    - Dedication, 1973-1974 (Box 24, Folder 335)
    - Design and Construction, undated, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 336)
    - Design and Construction, 1972-1975, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 337)
    - Blueprints, 1973, 1975 (Oversize 1)
- Series VII: Astronomy, undated, 1970, 1972
  - Eclipse, 1970 March 7 (Box 25, Folder 342)
  - Eclipse, 1972 July 10 (Box 25, Folder 343)
  - Photography, undated (Box 25, Folder 344)
- Series VIII: Surveying, undated
  - Surveying, undated (Box 25, Folder 345)
  - Surveying, undated (Box 25, Folder 346)